you stop?
Whoa!
Another round.
Black Maria.
Wait a minute.
Don't you have a job to do a job?
Why whatever could you mean?
You're supposed to be looking for my son
But wouldn't it be nicer
if I stayed here with
you the other toby robo
may be insufferable,
so I'll stay here and serve you.
Fair enough, let's not
stand on ceremony today!
So what do you say you having fun?
Oh, you bet I am, my good man.
For 20 long years, we've been haunted
by the ghosts of the Kozuki clan.
But they've been vanquished at last.
We have much to celebrate.
Kanjuro deceived them
to the very last second.
His grand performance has come to an end,
so I imagine he'll be
joining us at any moment.
The same goes for the
battleship captains who
sent those Akazaya
samurai to a watery grave.
Konjuro's impressive.
To think I almost killed him by accident
in our battle all those years ago.
But that doesn't mean Odin
trusted him with everything.
Certainly not with the secrets he
discovered on his trip across the seas.
But if Kanjuro wasn't told, then the
other samurai weren't told either?
Still thinking about that? Of course.
Odin knew the exact
location of Laugh Tale.
The last island that Roger's crew reached.
Who is this guy?
Do pardon the intrusion.
I must converse with Lord Orochi.
Kandero, you made it.
Is he one of us either way?
He's trying to start a fight.
The man works for order.
See you, morons!
Everyone stand down.
Please forgive me my lord.
I'm quite late.
I Lost my way.
This castle is much like a maze
Furthermore,
I was mistaken for an
enemy more than once and
was forced to strike
down a number of guards.
Again, my apologies.
Oh, well, that is too bad for them.
I see that you've brought a gift for me.
As you requested, this
is Kozuki Momonosuke.
Can you believe he's Odin's son?
The boy cut the ropes and
attempted to escape along the way.
Rest assured, he was disciplined.
But do not fret, he still breathes.
How could you do something so cruel to your
former lord and heir of the Kozuki clan?
Quite a heartless one
you turned out to be.
Now that my role is over, he's
naught but a lowly brat to me.
I'm still surprised I
remember you from back then.
It's hard to believe you
were one of the Akazaya Nine.
Twenty years ago, was it?
Our battle.
And you, I remember our encounter as well.
Some son of the great Kozuki
Oden you turned out to be.
You haven't changed one bit, have you?
Quite a disappointment, isn't he?
Seems that the only thing of
value that he has is his name.
That poor child.
Oh, how could you dare beat
this little boy black and blue?
I'll toast to that, my good man.
This one's for you.
To conjure our sinister spine.
You do excellent work.
Please, Lord Orochi.
I do not deserve such praise,
for I bring you unfortunate news.
The Straw Hat's appearance prevented
me from halting the Akasaya samurai.
I have failed you.
You should have called me Shula!
That's not all.
The rebel forces are advancing towards
Onigashima with the aid of 5,400 troops!
You blasted fool!
Your absolute incompetence
will be the death of me!
I sincerely apologize.
But you informed me of the
rendezvous point at Tokage Port!
Why didn't you slay them all?
Your excuse better be damn good!
I'm loathe to admit it,
but Kin'emon outsmarted me.
This is a shock since I have
known him for many years.
Cunning is not a word I'd use
to describe his character.
That sounds like a weak excuse.
Now, Kanjuro, what do you know?
Are the samurai on their way here?
Is there something else
you're not telling me?
No reason to lose your
head yet, Shogun Orochi.
Fukurokuju.
We haven't seen a single suspicious
ship at the dock thus far.
Our only concern is that
the trio of battleships
that we sent out earlier
have yet to come back.
Not to alarm you,
but there's a report that four pirates
have been sighted on the performance floor.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Eustass Captain Kidd.
Murder machine killer!
It's quite likely that
their pirate crews are also
in tow and have infiltrated
the island somehow?
If you knew all that,
why didn't you tell me?
Master, queen was supposed
to be handling the situation,
so I thought it'd be better not to
interrupt the banquet with this nonsense!
Sir, whether they're here or
not, we're more than prepared!
Our entire...
force is here on Onigashima.
Whatever challenge is presented,
this is the safest place in the
country at this moment.
That's a good point.
Have a drink, Orochi.
Just relax. Let me pour
you a cup.
No, I don't want to hear
reassurances and platitudes.
I won't be at ease until I
know Oh, the samurai are dead.
They will locate me.
I must have faith.
You gotta find a way to survive, okay?
Just hang on, and we'll come rescue you!
I will persevere.
Black Maria, give him to me.
There's one thing we must not forget.
This pathetic little brat
is still the enemy's leader.
Don't prepare the stage for an execution!
I'll bring an end to the Kozuki
bloodline in front of everyone!
Then the samurai loyalty will
crumble right before my eyes!
Then this will all be over!
Luffy
Everyone
Father
stupid cat, are you cara here of course
we just climbed up the waterfall?
do you cara even know what day it is?
why it's the night of the fire festival?
obviously so we made it just in time; i'm
afraid the verdict is still out on that.
We're almost there.
We're on our way to the
northwest end of Onigashima.
Sounds great.
I'll see you gotta there.
No, cat!
We can't wait! Listen up!
Kalik, I see our old friend
is as flippant as ever.
Shall we place bets on if
he makes it there in time?
Ka-ba-ba-ba!
I haven't seen Kitty since
we were separated years ago.
I imagine he got big like Dock did.
I can't wait.
This is a damn mess.
Did he leave late or what?
The raid is starting, so how the
hell is he going to make it in time?
He's in a normal ship.
The sea currents are far too
strong, except in the front.
In that case,
I hope Kin'emon and Denjiro have reached
the back entrance without incident.
Indeed.
We're Lord Odin's retainers.
We should avenge our
Lord's death together.
Lord Momonosuke, we shall be there soon.
Are they all right? Hmm?
You gotta expect it otherwise.
We were told that everyone
made it to the island,
so it's safe to assume that
the raid is well in progress.
They call that lonely little
isle Onigashima now, huh?
Funny how you guys left long before I
did, but we made it at the same time.
I asked you to send that message to Luffy,
but I guess there is no
need for that in the end.
You're gonna...
Yeah!
I almost forgot.
No reason to hang on to this, then.
I still find it hard to believe
you got involved, Marco.
Really?
I always did like Odin, though.
This whole time I was ignorant to how bad
things had gotten around the land of Wano.
Word rarely makes it past
the borders, if ever.
So there's no way I would have known.
Deserves much better than this.
The damn Kaido is to
blame for its suffering.
Hold on to those feelings and
use them when we get to the Isle.
Let's not delay our vengeance any further.
We should discuss the plan.
The raid's already underway.
How do we join them but
keep it on the down-low?
I got something up my sleeve.
You gotta just follow my lead.
As planned, Denjiro leads his
samurai, the Southern Forces,
towards the rear of the castle.
This was not in the blueprints.
Take cover!
Toby Rope, this means trouble!
Don't you dare come back
here until you find him.
Perfect, now this I can work with.
I know this idiot!
Let me handle this who's there.
Do not be alarmed Yoshiro
been a while hasn't it?
Hey Sasaki.
Hey, it is you.
I was told you weren't coming
this year It's a surprise.
So don't tell anyone
what's with the kid up.
You look weird without
your pompadour I find
it much stranger that
you're not at the feast.
Yeah. Yeah Well,
I can't enjoy myself
to the commander's son
turns up You wanna throw one back with me?
I'd love to. Listen up!
I'll catch up with you guys later!
Head to the Skull Dome without me!
Despite an unexpected obstacle and an
encounter with Sasaki of the Tobiropo,
Kyoshiro quickly turns
the situation around.
thanks to the trust he built among
the beast pirates over many years.
He quietly leads his foe into a trap.
See, prismstone?
What the hell are you doing?
Get off!
Fetch the restraints. Sir!
This some kind of joke? Release me!
Bind his mouth, too. Yes, sir!
Kyoshiro, answer me!
Calm down, Sasaki.
Tell me, what do you know about
the land of Wano's history?
Huh? That tattoo!
After effortlessly besting
one of the fearsome Tobiroko,
Denjiro splits his group into two
just as the eastern forces did.
You can enter the dome from there.
Best of luck to you.
The ambush on Kaido draws ever closer as
the southern forces steadily close in.
No!
We're not through! Come here!
I knew that it wouldn't play!
We're gonna die!
Oh, raccoon!
Time to die!
They distracted her.
I hope they're safe.
Fierce and mature.
How admirable of them both.
Even fleeing in terror,
they lured her away.
We're in your debt.
Thank you, Commander Chopper.
And you, Driver Uzzah,
let us march forth, sir!
Onward, men!
We must not let their honorable
sacrifice go to waste!
Maybe we should stop and assist them.
They surely need our
help with that monster.
What if she's too much woman
for those boys to handle?
She has a point!
It is Big Mom!
Then help how exactly?
I don't think there's anything we can do.
We'll have to thank them for the
diversion when they get back.
Jeez, why is it so hot in here?
Nabi, I love you! We've got trouble!
Finally found you!
Hey, Mama!
The lady who kidnapped
Zeus is right over here!
That's the leg! Papa!
Can't you do that down a
different hallway, you idiot?
What was that, Papa?
How about you say that to my
cute little face? Just shut up!
I'm ever so tired!
How heartless!
Would you treat me like
this if I was dying?
Poor little oldie!
Don't be like that.
If you're so tired, just sit there.
That's not what you're supposed to say!
Oh crap!
This is the part where you offer
to give me a piggyback ride!
Hey, you're choking, wait! Stop!
Ease your grip, sis!
Say you're sorry!
Come on, stop messing around!
Papa!
You gotta stay with me, dammit!
Oh, my poor sweet little Papa!
Oh, no!
Oh, here lies Papa.
He sacrificed his life for his
favorite person in the world.
Huh?
Can't you see I'm grieving here?
Who the heck are you?
That has to be only Gashima.
Curse you, King.
Mock, too.
And that damn Straw Hat.
Mama's Alliance be damned.
I'm going to wreak havoc
as soon as I get there.
Anyone who dares to cross us will
get the worst licking of their lives.
Wait a second.
There's a problem.
I'm pretty sure Big Mom was
headed towards Nami's group.
She's probably gonna
try to take back Zeus.
So that means they're in danger.
The damage we just took.
I think it accidentally activated
the transformation switch.
Don't worry, they're gonna be fine.
Sanji's with them, remember?
I guess you're right.
Although I hope he doesn't
get distracted by the
Pleasure Hall and can
focus on saving Momonosuke.
That is the risk with him, unfortunately.
Let's just hope for the best.
Alright.
At least Kinemon's group can keep moving
forward thanks to us, so that's something.
Glad we showed them the Brachio tank.
Bet they thought it was real cool.
Heck yeah!
Between Commander Chopper,
Sniper-slash-Driver Usopp, and our tank!
Those Samurai must be in awe!
Nothing can stop us now!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
Follow me, everyone!
Come here, little umbrella!
You too, old Chew!
Hurry along now!
I want you too, Dirtwall. Yes!
And you, Captain!
Lantern!
Join me and I'll give you all life!
Come along now, little homies.
Mama! Look! Right here!
Knock it off!
Stop drawing attention to us, stupid son!
We gotta do something.
If Mama steals me back, then
I'll be as good as dead for sure.
Is that overripe, mature woman
really as dangerous as they say?
She's all that and then
some, I promise you.
Hold on.
Wasn't Sanji supposed to be here with us?
Yeah, I think.
Sorry for making you worry.
I'll find those lovely
ladies no matter what.
Dependable as ever, I guess.
We'll just have to run.
We still have a mission
to rescue Lord Momonosuke.
Hey!
Hey! Mama!
Over this way!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
There's no need to rush.
The performance floor
is up ahead, correct?
They'll be right where we want them.
I'm seeing people with weird
abilities everywhere I go.
Just call us gifters.
We all at one time
shared that same desire.
Every one of us things will be so
much easier for you if you defect.
There's nearly 500 of us.
It ain't so bad—have
a fresh start with us.
Kid,
you sure you still want
to take them head on?
Sneaking in would be easier; we've already
lost a bunch of crewmates to the chaos.
I'm sure they can make it through
on their own, but we gotta.
gotta We're gonna stick
together till we meet up again.
If I kill you, I'll get promoted for sure.
Nothing personal, of course.
Please stop!
The commander is looking for you!
Leave me alone, all right?
I've got places to be!
Master, please wait!
If you let your guard down,
you might get yourself killed!
Oh baby!
My poor sweet little baby brother!
Did you get a boo-boo?
I'm ever, ever so happy that you're okay!
What are you looking at?
How dare you!
Whom do you think you are
hurting him like that?
You're out of line, pal.
Only I'm allowed to bully Papa.
Huh?
You were the one surfing
on him down the stairs.
I didn't touch him.
Who are you?
What unit are you with?
Who's your commanding officer?
I don't think he's one of ours. Huh? What?
He's an intruder.
The Nerve.
The name's Luffy.
The man who's going to
be king of the pirates.
Excuse you?
Oh, boy.
Do you have the teeniest clue
whose mansion you stepped foot in?
Newsflash!
It belongs to Commander Kaido, who's
going to be the real king of the pirates!
You're the dumbest dummy in the world!
I'm going to fully drive stallion, too!
Headfoot!
Ultimoder!
Hey, sis, be careful of him, all right?
Yeah, I got it.
Wanna help, Papa? Sure.
Excuse me, is all this really necessary?
Harry, why would you resort to
transforming when he's down?
Lady Ulti?
Page one, sir?
Maybe I'm out of line.
This seems excessive.
Shut your damn mouth!
I can make up my own mind.
And we already decided that
this guy's a dangerous enemy.
I don't know, ma 'am.
He looks pretty dead to me.
Hey, you cracked his head open!
Then where the hell is all
that Haki coming from, huh?
Hot heart! Hey!
You guys are tougher than you look.
Didn't see that coming.
Guess I underestimated you.
It won't happen again.
This is an emperor's home turf after all.
Listen up shitheads!
Sorry to interrupt your
scheduled drinking.
But Shogun Orochi has a
special event for you.
Hello.
Testing.
Is this thing on?
Good.
Welcome all.
I come to you this
evening with a real treat.
Does anyone recognize this boy?
You're looking at Kozuki Oden's son.
He was thought to be dead 20 years ago.
Now come, come!
Fix this!
Drop them!
OLEPHANT GUNS!!!
Are you okay? That looked bad!
Page one, sir!
Listen here, you slimeball!
You've got some nerve-hurting Papa!
I'm gonna crush you!
Lady Olsen pulled out her dinosaur board!
Please, this place can't
take this kind of damage!
Stop!
That's a good grip!
She's really strong!
Naughty Meteor!
Crap!
What? Deer!
Ahhhhh!
Thunder!
Aqua!
Nooo!
Straw Hat Luffy
It's really you, isn't it?
Uh, yeah?
They're getting away!
Seize them!
Forgive me.
I swear I mean you no harm.
Alright.
You seem like a good person. Put me down.
You hear me?
There's something I gotta do.
The day has finally come.
Now, I understand this may sound odd, but
I've anticipated this for quite some time.
I've been waiting for you.
My name is Yamato.
I'm Kaido's son!